CURTIS LANG

An Assistant Store Manager with three years of experience, specializing in customer service, operations management, team leadership, and communication. A strong background in managing and training diverse teams to enhance store operations and deliver high-quality service to customers.

123 Your Street, Portland, OR 12345 cu rt is la n gl@exa m pie. com (123)456-7890

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ASSISTANT STORE MANAGER

Peet's Coffee, Portland. OR May 2019 -Present

- Coordinate with the store manager to oversee all aspects of store operations, including inventory management, sales forecasting, staff scheduling, and customer service related issues
- Lead a team of six cashiers, baristas, and cooks each shift, define workflows,
 evaluate performance, and provide mentorship to facilitate professional growth
- Drive training initiatives to enhance product knowledge and sales techniques for team members, resulting in a 10% increase in monthly sales

SHIFT LEADER

Peet's Coffee, Portland, OR May 2018 - May 2019

- Served as shift lead to provide operational support to the assistant store manager and store manager, which included prioritizing tasks for team members and ensuring compliance with company policies and procedures
- Interface with customers on a daily basis to ensure a high-quality experience and identify resolutions to order issues

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (B,S,) Business Ad mi nistration University of Portland, Portland, OR September 2014 - May 2018

KEY SKILLS

- Customer Service
- Team Leadership
- ♦ Operations Management
- ♦ Process Improvement
- ♦ Sta ff Devel opment

CERTIFICATIONS

♦ ServSafe Certifi c atio n. 2019